

Education Bachelor CS

University Princess Sumaya University For Technology Bachelors

Degree in Computer Science (82.3)

Graduation Year 2021 Fall semester

Android Course

Date 2015 April Pearson

Details Assured

IELTS

Date 2021 Dec Details Scored 8

About me

Self taught programmer, started learning programming at the age of 12, and Interested in Tech and keeping up with cutting edge technologies.

Skills

Programing Languages Dart (Flutter), Java, C#, Python, Javascript, C/C++, Kotlin, PHP

Strong Points Problem Solver, Clean Coder, Research, Strong Communication Skills.

Frameworks Spring Framework, Flutter, Express.JS, React.JS.

Projects https://kaliham.io/#projects

Additional Skills AWS, Git, MySql, PostgreSQL, unix, vim, ZSH

Experience

Amazon Internship Sep, 2020 - Dec, 2020:

- Backend: Spring Framework REST-API, elastic search, JUnit 5.
- Frontend: PHP Yii, Javascript, jQuery, Chart.js.
- Additional: Git Version control, Working in Scrum methodology, Unit Testing.

EHS Internship Feb, 2020 - Mar, 2020:

- Fullstack: ASP .Net, CSHTML, Javascript, Entity Framework.
- · Additional: Git version control

PWCInternship Apr, 2020 - Jul, 2020:

- · Digital Consultant working, on SF Marketing Cloud.
- DevOps Using Azure, Leading SCRUM Meetings.

MadHook Internship Nov, 2021 - Jan, 2022:

- Game Development with Unity.
- · Working with Firebase, PlayFab.

MadHook GameDeveloper Jan, 2021 - Sep, 2022:

- Game dev with Unity & deploying on iOS app store and androids play store
- Developing Multiplayer Features Games.
- · Designing and developing systems and mechanics for games...
- · Integrating apis and libraries within games.

Personal Information

Omar Taher Ibrahim

https://github.com/Kaliham

kaliham.io omar@kaliham io (347)609-1216

18/09/1998